Aviel Cohanian Full Stack | Frontend Web Developer

Email: avial151515@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/aviel-cohanian Github: https://github.com/avielCohanian Portfolio: https://portfolio-aviel.netlify.app

Tel: 050-3431443

Summary:

Full Stack Web Developer, with experience in writing single-page-applications using the latest WEB technologies such as Node.js, ES6, Vue.js, Vuex, Angular and MongoDb. Hard worker, passionate about solving challenges, focusing on problem solving and detailed orientation, self-learner, team player with strong communication skills.

Checkout my latest project: https://trelix--4.herokuapp.com/

Graduate of the Coding Academy - An intensive coding bootcamp (640 hours) that qualifies Full Stack developers. Built several projects, all code is available on Github.

Tech skills:

- Programming in modern JavaScript (ES5, ES6), building a full scale web app.
- JS Frameworks and state Management: Vue.js, Vuex, Angular, React.
- Building multi Page Applications.
- HTML5, CSS3 and SASS, From Photoshop to a live page, Responsive design and "mobile first".
- Bootstrap and jQuery.
- Server side, APIs and REST with Node.JS.
- •Database management with MongoDb and SQL..

Professional Experience:

A fighter in a classified position in the Air Force, release in the rank of staff sergeant, IDF | 2018 - 2021

- The service demanded leading a team of soldiers.
- Making important decisions under pressure.
- Working with variety of people.
- The service included Persistence, Time management, Responsibility, Teamwork.

Sales person, Isracard | 2017 - 2018

- Working in a fast-paced environment.
- Building customer loyalty.
- Dealing with inquiries E2E.
- Marketing products while dealing with customers.
- Front line customer support.

Education:

Coding Academy (2021) | Full Stack Web Coding Bootcamp.

Bar ilan High School, Tel-Aviv (2013 - 2018) | Majors: Computer and Chemistry.

